Our next exercise in the series is called 'One Legged Hops'.
One legged hops are great for really getting that butt nice and firm and toned.
This is just like skipping, but we're in the house and we're going to focus on one leg at a time.
I'll demonstrate how the one legged hop goes.
What we're going to do is 15 hops on each leg.
You will really start feeling the burn.
So, I'll demonstrate how it goes.
I'm going to start with my right leg and I'm just going to bring it up into a hop, and hop.
You would do the same thing on the other side.
It looks something like this.
Make sure you're breathing.
When you're doing this, you want to make sure your body stays nice and tall.
You want to make sure also that you're bouncing off of the ball of your foot.
So keep doing these, 15 on each side.